https://www.voice-online.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Subscribe
Search for:
Music, UK News
Headie One statues pop up around London in promotion of his upcoming album
Arts & Culture
Black men, mental health and COVID-19 explored in new theatre show
5
UK News
Campaigners say asylum seeker’s legal victory against Home Office is ‘beacon of hope’
The ultimate events guide!
What's On
Privacy Policy
Privacy Notice for The Voice
We endeavour to maintain the highest standards of confidentiality and to respect the privacy of our readers, web site visitors and associated persons who deal with us. Our commitment to privacy includes being transparent about the nature and extent of the personal data processing we undertake. This privacy statement aims to inform you about how we collect, store, use and disclose information about you when you:
interact or use our websites;register and/or attend any of our events, webinars, or conferences, andif you use any of our products, services or applications (collectively the “services”) in any manner.
Who we are
GV Media is a member company of The Jamaica National Group Ltd (the parent company). We publish The Voice Newspaper (The Voice). Our Head Office is in Jamaica. GV Media takes its data protection and information security responsibilities very seriously. The effective management of all personal data, including its security and confidentiality, lies at the very heart of our business and underpins our practices and processes.
As a group with a global presence, we are subject to the varying requirements of data protection legislation in the jurisdictions where we operate. Our aim is to be as consistent as possible and obey all applicable laws and apply the highest standard of privacy laws to our approach.
What information do we collect?
We gather various types of information, that may identify you as an individual (“personal information”). We gather information from the following sources:
From Events: We may collect any personal information that you choose to provide to us.
From our Website. We may collect information you choose to upload to our website to subscribe directly to our services or competitions. When you visit the Websites, we may collect certain information related to your device, such as your device’s IP address, what pages your device visited, and the time that your device visited our Website. These include:
Usage information – we keep track of user activity in relation to the types of services our customers and their users use, and the performance metrics related to their use of the Services.
Log information – we log information about our customers and their users when you use one of the services, including Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. Information collected by cookies and other similar technologies – we use various technologies to collect information which may include saving cookies to users’ computers.
For further information, please read the section headed “Cookies” in the “Your Privacy Rights” section of this statement.
From the Services we provide: We receive and store information you provide directly to us. For example, when you attend an event we may collect your personal information if you volunteer it.
From our competitions. If you apply for a competition, you will fill out an online form which we will ask if you’d like to sign up to our database and receive further information from us.
The types of information we may collect directly from our customers include; Email address, Name and telephone number. Information is uploaded to our systems in connection with the services. We retain this information in line with our retention policy.
How do we use the information?
We may use the information we collect from our web site visitors and readers with the services we provide for a range of reasons, including to:
communicate a request back to and to manage the relationship with you or your business; manage our customers’ use of the services, respond to enquiries and comments and provide customer service and support; process and complete transactions and send related information, including transaction confirmations and invoices; to develop new ways to meet our readers needs and to grow our business; keeping our records up to date; to carry out any legal obligations we may have; to develop and carry out marketing activities of our group company and share products discounts, promotions and events that we think may be of interest to you; developing products and content for our website; to study how our customers interact with our website; to enable us to provide marketing material that we may think may be of interest to you; to provide advice or guidance about our publications and services; for any other purpose about which we notify customers and users.
Lawful basis
Lawful basisOur lawful basis for processing your data includes:Your “Consent” when you opt-in to our mailing list for marketing, and“Performance of a Contract” where you engage with us to display advertising on our website or newsletter.
Retention policy
Retention periods for records are determined based on the type of record, the nature of the activity, product or service, the country in which the relevant company is located and the applicable local legal or regulatory requirements. We normally keep customer records for up to two years after analysis reveals that we have had no interaction with you.
If you apply for a freelance role with us and you ask us to retain your details on file, then we may hold this data for seven years.
If you engage with us on a commercial, basis, we keep details of the financial transactions and contract for seven years.
How do we share and disclose information to third parties?
We do not rent or sell your personal information to anyone. We may share and disclose information (including personal information) about our customers in the following limited circumstances:
we may share your information for compliance purposes to national law enforcement agencies in other countries if requested to do so;
We may share your information to our group company to provide you with offers, discounts, event invites and promotions if you have given us your consent to do so.
we may share your information with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who we employ to perform tasks on our behalf.
If GV Media receives your personal information and subsequently transfers that information to a third-party agent or service provider for processing, we remain committed to ensuring that such third-party agent or service provider processes your personal information to the standard required to meet GDPR and other local privacy laws.
International Data Transfers
We store your email name and address with our vendor, The Rocket Science Group LLC d/b/a MailChimp also known as “MailChimp”. Their privacy notice can be found here; https://www.iubenda.com/en/help/13638-privacy-policy-for-mailchimp
MailChimp is a US-based company, and they store your information on servers that are based in the USA, and they are signed up to the Privacy Shield agreement which commits the company to a high level of privacy safeguards.
Linked Websites
For your convenience, hyperlinks may be posted on the website that link to other websites. We are not responsible for these sites, and this privacy notice does not apply to the privacy practices of any linked sites or of any companies that we do not own or control. Linked sites may collect information in addition to that which we collect on our website. We encourage you to seek out and read the privacy notice of each linked site that you visit to understand how the information that is collected about you is used and protected.
For our dating service, you can find the privacy policy of Venntro Media Group Ltd, also called the Heart 2 Heart service here.https://app.voice-online.co.uk/help/privacy.cfm
Business Transfers:We may choose to buy or sell assets and may share or transfer customer information in connection with the evaluation of this transactions. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, personal information could be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.
Jamaica National Group Companies:
We may also share your personal data with our parent company or group company for the purposes consistent with this Privacy Notice. If we send your data to our group companies outside of the EU, you are protected by model contract clauses.
SecurityWe use appropriate technical, organisational and administrative security measures to protect any information we hold in our records from loss, misuse, and unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We have written procedures and policies which are regularly audited, and the audits are reviewed at a senior level.
We use CCTV as a deterrent to protect our staff, customers, equipment and your personal data at our offices.
Exercising your Privacy Rights
What choices do I have? You can always opt not to disclose information to us, but keep in mind some information may be needed to transact with us or to take advantage of some of our offers and discounts. You can opt-out of emailing lists at any time by clicking unsubscribe on our email communications.
Cookies
We use cookies and other internet tracking software to collect data while you are using our websites or mobile apps. Cookies allow us to store information about the computer device you use to access our website so that you can conduct business with us easily. They allow us to recognise when you revisit our websites and to evaluate our websites’ advertising and promotional effectiveness. We use both our own (first party) and partner companies’ (third party) cookies to support this activity. Our main third-party advertisers who use your cookies to provide advertisements on your website are: Tribal Fusion and Advertising.Com.
We do not use Cookies to:
track your Internet usage after leaving the website, orstore personal information others may read and understand.processing of personal data associated with the use of these cookies occurs based on our Legitimate Interests to administer the website.
Our cookies are listed below.
Cookie Name _utmaDefault Expiration time NeverDescription This cookie is what’s called a “persistent” cookie, as in, it never expires. This cookie keeps track of the number of times a visitor has been to the site pertaining to the cookie, when their first visit was, and when their last visit occurred.
Cookie Name _utmb
Default Expiration time Per Visit
Description
The _utmb and _utmc cookies are related, working together to calculate how long a visit takes. __utmb takes a timestamp of the exact moment in time when a visitor enters a site, while __utmc takes a timestamp of the exact moment in time when a visitor leaves a site.
Cookie Name _utmc Default Expiration time Per Visit DescriptionAs above the__utmc takes a timestamp of the exact moment in time when a visitor leaves a site.
Cookie Name _utmtDefault Expiration time 2 yearsDescription This is a cookie set by the Google Analytics service which enables website owners to track visitor behaviour and measure site performance. This cookie is used when site owners create custom visitor-level variables for customising what can be measured. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics. It has a default lifespan of two years, although this can be customised by site owners.
You can deactivate the non-technical cookies by not consenting to non-essential cookies when you first visit the site. When you first visit the site, it gives you an opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of cookies.
You may also set your browser’s setting to deactivate cookies. If you use that option, some functions of this website (e.g. login, memory of preferences etc.) may not be available. Detailed guidance on how to control cookies preferences for the most common browsers can be found at:
Google Chrome Mozilla Firefox MacOS Safari Microsoft Internet Explorer For other browsers please see www.allaboutcookies.org
You also have the option to install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on and thereby deactivate the use of Google analytics cookies and the associated data processing. You can find the Opt-out browser add-on here.https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
Your rights subject to the application of GDPR
How Can I Exercise My Data Subject Rights?
If you would like to access, review, update, rectify, and delete any personal information we hold about you, or exercise any other data subject right available to you under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you can email us at DPO@theVoice.com .Our privacy team will examine your request and respond to you as quickly as possible. You can also contact us on any of the telephone numbers or contact information supplied in the “Contact Us” section.
Please note that we may still use any aggregated and de-identified personal information that does not identify any individual. We may also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Automated decision making and profiling
Tailoring Products, Services, Offers and Marketing
We may place you in groups with similar customers. These are called customer segments. We use these to study and learn about our customers’ needs and behaviours, and to make decisions based on what we learn. This helps us to design products, services and offers for different customer segments, and to manage our relationships with them. It also helps us tailor the information that individuals receive or see on our own and other websites and mobile apps, including social media.
Marketing
Unless you have told us that you do not want to hear from us, we will send you relevant marketing information (including details of other products or services provided by us or other JN Group companies which we believe may be of interest to you), by mail, phone, email, text and other forms of electronic communication. If you change your mind about how you would like us to contact you, or you no longer wish to receive this information, you can request the necessary changes to be made by contacting us. For the contact information please look at the “Contact Us” section of this notice.
Contact Us
For any GDPR enquiry you can email us at; DPO@thevoice.com
You can also contact our Data Protection Officers at:
DPO@thevoice.comBarry McCormackThe Voice Unit 1 Bricklayers Arms, Mandela Way, SE1 5SR
Or
JNGroupDPO@JNgroup.com
L. Anthony Robinson
JN Group
2-4 Constant Spring Road
Kingston 10
Jamaica
You also have the right to make a complaint to an EU regulator if you are resident in the EU. If you are unhappy at the wa, we have dealt with your privacy, you can contact our Data Protection Officer or make a complaint to the Information Commissioners Office. The details are:
Information Commissioner’s Office
Wycliffe House
Water Lane
Wilmslow
Cheshire
SK9 5AF
Helpline number: 0044 (0)303 123 1113
Changes to this privacy statement occur from time to time as the business develops and grows and adds more processing. You are encouraged to check back regularly to see any changes that may have occurred.
Information pertaining to children
We do not knowingly hold information on children. If a parent of guardian believes we hold information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately and we will remove the information promptly.
Support The Voice The Voice Newspaper is committed to celebrating black excellence, campaigning for positive change and informing the black community on important issues. Your financial contributions are essential to protect the future of the publication as we strive to help raise the profile of the black communities across the UK. Any size donation is welcome and we thank you for your continued support.
Support
Sign-up
Support The Voice The Voice Newspaper is committed to celebrating black excellence, campaigning for positive change and informing the black community on important issues. Your financial contributions are essential to protect the future of the publication as we strive to help raise the profile of the black communities across the UK. Any size donation is welcome and we thank you for your continued support.
Support
Sign-up
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
About Us
Contact Us
ENTWURF: Design & Build
Copyright 2020
© GV Media Group Ltd. All rights reserved.
By continuing to use this website you agree to our cookie policy
OK
MORE INFO
